In this lesson, you've covered a lot of material.
在本课程中 您覆盖了大量的材料
You've learned about the similarities and
你了解到相似点
differences between regions and availability zones.
区域和可用性区域之间的差异
You've also seen how they form the underpinning of fault tolerance in AWS.
您还可以看到它们是如何在 AWS中形成容错的基础的
Making proper use of these physical assets
适当使用这些实物资产
allows you to create world-class worldwide platforms.
允许您创建世界级的全球平台
VPCs and the networking you can create in AWS are closely related.
VPC 和您可以在 AWS 中创建的网络密切相关
You've looked at many common aspects of creating independent network segments within AWS,
您已查看在 AWS 中创建独立网络段的许多常见方面
and how you can connect these segments together.
以及如何将这些分段连接在一起
Now that we've seen the base of high availability in AWS,
现在我们在 AWS中看到了高可用性的基础
we move on to building with
我们要继续建造
resilience services before we get to considering our business goals.
在我们考虑业务目标之前
Then, observability and recoverability
然后 可观察性和可恢复性